詹姆斯·韦布空间望远镜可观测视野范围是怎样的？
Which parts of the sky can the Webb Telescope see?
非等比例
詹姆斯·韦布空间望远镜与地球同步围绕太阳公转
The James Webb Space Telescope orbits the Sun in sync with Earth.
而位置远在100万英里(越150万公里)的月球轨道外
But 1 million miles further out beyond the moon.
望远镜的主镜与70英尺(21.2米)长的遮阳罩垂直 保持低温
The telescope's mirror is perpendicular to the 70-foot Sun shield which keeps it cool.
热侧
185°F
85°C
冷侧
-388°F
-233°C
望远镜的移动被限制在一定范围内
The telescope's movement is limited in certain directions
以保持镜面与仪器始终待在太阳阴影里
to keep the mirror and scientific instruments in the shade of the Sun shield,
免受太阳热量辐射影响
blocked from the heat of the Sun.
而望远镜还可以滚转 从而获取360度的环形视野
But Webb can rotate to get a 360-degree view of the sky.
随着望远镜绕太阳公转 不同的天体可以进入其可观测视野内
As Webb orbits the Sun, different celestial objects enter its available field of view.
望远镜的科学观测会有周密的策划
Science observations with the telescope will be carefully scheduled
保证最大化利用其观测时间
to make the most effective use of Webb's time.
非等比例
大约每半年 望远镜就能观测整片星空
Over the course of six months, Webb has access to the entire sky,
允许天文学家调查一系列探寻宇宙奥秘的问题
allowing astronomers to investigate a range of questions,
about how the universe works and are placed into cosmos.